module.exports = {
    quizQuestions: [{
        _id: "5c35bb79617fae59b4f35d07",
        correctAnswer: 4,
        difficultyLevel: 3,
        status: 1,
        question: "What color is the sky?",
        socSpecificOccupationCodeId: "5bff8841d4287a0b8c9c9daa",
        socCategoryCodeId: "5bd963dd1f19f826287dc4d1",
        occupationSkillId: "5bffb3cdd4287a0b8c9c9f55",
        option1: "Orange",
        option2: "Blue",
        option3: "Green",
        option4: "A or B",
        createdAt: "2019-01-09T09:14:33.044+00:00",
        updatedAt: "2019-01-09T09:14:33.044+00:00"
    }, {
        _id: "5c35bb79617fae59b4f35d07",
        correctAnswer: 3,
        difficultyLevel: 3,
        status: 1,
        question: "Who is buried in Ulysses S. Grant's tomb?",
        socSpecificOccupationCodeId: "5bff8841d4287a0b8c9c9daa",
        socCategoryCodeId: "5bd963dd1f19f826287dc4d1",
        occupationSkillId: "5bffb3cdd4287a0b8c9c9f55",
        option1: "George Washington",
        option2: "George Patton",
        option3: "Ulysses S. Grant",
        option4: "Nobody; he's sipping cocktails on the beach with Elvis",
        createdAt: "2019-01-09T09:14:33.044+00:00",
        updatedAt: "2019-01-09T09:14:33.044+00:00"
    }, {
        _id: "5c35bb79617fae59b4f35d07",
        correctAnswer: 4,
        difficultyLevel: 3,
        status: 1,
        question: "17 x 3 = ?",
        socSpecificOccupationCodeId: "5bff8841d4287a0b8c9c9daa",
        socCategoryCodeId: "5bd963dd1f19f826287dc4d1",
        occupationSkillId: "5bffb3cdd4287a0b8c9c9f55",
        option1: "Circle",
        option2: "Blue",
        option3: 'The letter "R"',
        option4: "51",
        createdAt: "2019-01-09T09:14:33.044+00:00",
        updatedAt: "2019-01-09T09:14:33.044+00:00"
    }, {
        _id: "5c35bb79617fae59b4f35d07",
        correctAnswer: 2,
        difficultyLevel: 3,
        status: 1,
        question: "What color was George Washington's white horse?",
        socSpecificOccupationCodeId: "5bff8841d4287a0b8c9c9daa",
        socCategoryCodeId: "5bd963dd1f19f826287dc4d1",
        occupationSkillId: "5bffb3cdd4287a0b8c9c9f55",
        option1: "Purple",
        option2: "White",
        option3: "Black",
        option4: "Plaid",
        createdAt: "2019-01-09T09:14:33.044+00:00",
        updatedAt: "2019-01-09T09:14:33.044+00:00"
    }, {
        _id: "5c35bb79617fae59b4f35d07",
        correctAnswer: 1,
        difficultyLevel: 3,
        status: 1,
        question: "On what date is the 4th of July?",
        socSpecificOccupationCodeId: "5bff8841d4287a0b8c9c9daa",
        socCategoryCodeId: "5bd963dd1f19f826287dc4d1",
        occupationSkillId: "5bffb3cdd4287a0b8c9c9f55",
        option1: "July 4th",
        option2: "December 25th",
        option3: "November 33rd",
        option4: "Monday",
        createdAt: "2019-01-09T09:14:33.044+00:00",
        updatedAt: "2019-01-09T09:14:33.044+00:00"
    }, {
        _id: "5c35bb79617fae59b4f35d07",
        correctAnswer: 3,
        difficultyLevel: 3,
        status: 1,
        question: "A rectangular house is built. All four walls have a southern exposure. A bear walks by. What color is the bear?",
        socSpecificOccupationCodeId: "5bff8841d4287a0b8c9c9daa",
        socCategoryCodeId: "5bd963dd1f19f826287dc4d1",
        occupationSkillId: "5bffb3cdd4287a0b8c9c9f55",
        option1: "Brown",
        option2: "Black",
        option3: "White",
        option4: "Bears? Did you say BEARS?",
        createdAt: "2019-01-09T09:14:33.044+00:00",
        updatedAt: "2019-01-09T09:14:33.044+00:00"
    }, {
        _id: "5c35bb79617fae59b4f35d07",
        correctAnswer: 2,
        difficultyLevel: 3,
        status: 1,
        question: "How many birthdays does the average person have each year?",
        socSpecificOccupationCodeId: "5bff8841d4287a0b8c9c9daa",
        socCategoryCodeId: "5bd963dd1f19f826287dc4d1",
        occupationSkillId: "5bffb3cdd4287a0b8c9c9f55",
        option1: "12",
        option2: "1",
        option3: "365",
        option4: "24",
        createdAt: "2019-01-09T09:14:33.044+00:00",
        updatedAt: "2019-01-09T09:14:33.044+00:00"
    }, {
        _id: "5c35bb79617fae59b4f35d07",
        correctAnswer: 3,
        difficultyLevel: 3,
        status: 1,
        question: "Some months have 31 days. How many have 28 days?",
        socSpecificOccupationCodeId: "5bff8841d4287a0b8c9c9daa",
        socCategoryCodeId: "5bd963dd1f19f826287dc4d1",
        occupationSkillId: "5bffb3cdd4287a0b8c9c9f55",
        option1: "1",
        option2: "2",
        option3: "12",
        option4: "It depends on whether or not it's Leap Year",
        createdAt: "2019-01-09T09:14:33.044+00:00",
        updatedAt: "2019-01-09T09:14:33.044+00:00"
    }, {
        _id: "5c35bb79617fae59b4f35d07",
        correctAnswer: 4,
        difficultyLevel: 3,
        status: 1,
        question: "Before Mt. Everest was discovered, what was the tallest peak in the world?",
        socSpecificOccupationCodeId: "5bff8841d4287a0b8c9c9daa",
        socCategoryCodeId: "5bd963dd1f19f826287dc4d1",
        occupationSkillId: "5bffb3cdd4287a0b8c9c9f55",
        option1: "Mt. Kilamanjaro",
        option2: "K2",
        option3: "Mt. Fiji",
        option4: "None of the Above",
        createdAt: "2019-01-09T09:14:33.044+00:00",
        updatedAt: "2019-01-09T09:14:33.044+00:00"
    }, {
        _id: "5c35bb79617fae59b4f35d07",
        correctAnswer: 4,
        difficultyLevel: 3,
        status: 1,
        question: "This cloud-baesd SaaS is: ",
        socSpecificOccupationCodeId: "5bff8841d4287a0b8c9c9daa",
        socCategoryCodeId: "5bd963dd1f19f826287dc4d1",
        occupationSkillId: "5bffb3cdd4287a0b8c9c9f55",
        option1: "The best HR software product ever",
        option2: "Going to disrupt a $200 billion domestic industry",
        option3: "Going to revolutionize the way employers and employees connect",
        option4: "All of the Above",
        createdAt: "2019-01-09T09:14:33.044+00:00",
        updatedAt: "2019-01-09T09:14:33.044+00:00"
    }]
}
